Inventory of the Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
- Divisions and Departments
  - Romance Languages
  - Russian
  - Science in Society
  - Sociology
  - Theater and Dance
  - Theater and Dance - Children's Dance Workshop
  - Theater and Dance - Dance Workshop
  - Tutorials
  - Twelve College Exchange
  - University Major
  - Western Civilization
  - Women's Studies
  - Writing Program
- Educational Policy Committee
  - Educational Policy Committee (EPC)
  - EPC Reports 1955-
- Examinations
  - Examinations, grades, averages, academic standards
  - Examination schedules, 1835-1932
  - Examination schedules, 1933-
- Faculty: General
  - Faculty Misc, to 1970
  - Faculty Misc, 1971-1993
  - Faculty Misc, 1994-
  - Academic Affairs Online, 2000-
  - Advising of students
  - American Association of University Professors
  - Appraisal by students
  - By-laws
  - Faculty Club
  - Faculty Committees
  - Committees: Administrators and Faculty of Color Alliance
  - Committees: Committee on Rights and Responsibilities
  - Committees: Faculty Planning Committee
  - Committees: Graduate Instruction
  - Committees: Honors and General Education
  - Committees: Institutional Priorities Advisory Committee
  - Committees: Library
  - Committees: Student Affairs
  - Department Guides
  - Experts
  - Junior Faculty
  - Length of Service
  - Mid-winter bulletin
  - New members, to 1984
  - New members, 1984-1996
  - New members, 1997-
  - Professorships (endowed chairs)
  - Retiring
  - Salaries, 1831-1985
  - Salaries, 1985-
  - Salaries and benefits: grants
  - Salaries and benefits, group insurance
  - Salaries: salary lists
  - Salaries and benefits: Academic freedom and tenure
  - Salaries and benefits: sabbaticals and leaves
  - Salaries and benefits: research
  - Salaries and benefits: childrens tuition scholarships
  - Salaries and benefits: pensions, annuities, retirement, etc.
  - Salaries and benefits: benefits, part-time
  - Salaries and benefits: Denison Awards
  - Social Events
  - Teaching Apprentices
  - Women members
  - Faculty groups photos, 1863-1875
  - Faculty groups photos, 1876-1884
  - Faculty groups photos, 1891-1899
  - Faculty groups photos, 1900-1915
  - Faculty groups photos, 1917-1922
  - Faculty groups photos, 1931-1943
  - Faculty groups photos, 1944-1956
  - Faculty groups photos, 1958-1967
  - Faculty groups photos, 1968-
  - Staff photos
- Faculty: Individuals
  - Abelove, Henry
  - Abizadeh, Arash
  - Adamany, David Walter
  - Adams, David
  - Adams, J. Robert
  - Adams, Bro (William)
  - Adelstein, Richard P.
  - Adzinyah, Abraham, Kobena
  - Agoston, Max Karl
  - Albert, Nancy
  - Alejandro, Pedro
  - Allcock, John
  - Allen, Archibald W.
  - Allewell, Norma
  - Alonso, Carlos
  - Anderson, Karen L.
  - Angle, Stephen
  - Antelpi, Abdullah
  - Anthony, James B.
  - Anthony, Kelly
  - Antonaccio, Carla
  - Archambault, Reginald D.
  - Ariel, David
  - Armstrong, Andrew Campbell
  - Armstrong, Michael
  - Arnold, Frederic Kappeler
  - Arnold, Herbert Anton
  - Arrowsmith, William Ayres
  - Arthur, Marilyn B.
  - Atwater, Wilbur Olin
  - Atwater, Wilbur Olin photos
  - Atwater Memorial Lectures
  - Bacon, Grace
  - Baierlein, Ralph F.
  - Bailey, Stephen Kemp
  - Baker, Ann
  - Baker, Jeffrey J. W.
  - Balasaraswet
  - Balch, Franklin Greere III
  - Balsley, James R.
  - Barnes, Sally
  - Bank, Stephen Paul
  - Banks, Theodore Howard
  - Bannerman, Harold M.
  - Baranger, Anne M.
  - Barber, William Joseph
  - Barlow, Jon Kent
  - Barnstone, Willis Robert
  - Barron, William Jr.
  - Bartholomew, Reginals
  - Bartlett, Horace
  - Bascom, Barbara
  - Basinger, Jeanine
  - Beauchamp, Kara M.
  - Beckham, Edgar
  - Behringer, Robert
  - Bell, Barbara Currier
  - Bell, Herbert Clifford Francis
  - Bellani, Raj
  - Belt, William
  - Bendally, Lewis Kent
  - Benedict, Francis Gano
  - Benitez Hodge, Grissel
  - Benson, Robert Louis
  - Benson, Ruth Crego
  - Berenbaum, Michael
  - Berger, Robert Jules
  - Berlind, Allan
  - Bernstein, Howard
  - Berry, Spencer Julian
  - Bertin, Joanne
  - Bertman, Bernard T.
  - Best, Catherine
  - Best, Jonathan W.
  - Beuning, Kristina
  - Beveridge, David
  - Biddiscombe, John
  - Blackwell, Ed
  - Blanchard, Carver
  - Blankenagel, John Charles
  - Blechman, Elaine
  - Blumel, Reinhold
  - Brobrick, Elizabeth
  - Bock, Robert J.
  - Bodzniak, David Alan
  - Bonin, John Paul
  - Basakowski, Phil
  - Boswell, Donna A.
  - Bosworth, Mary
  - Bowman, Isaiah
  - Boyd, Richard W.
  - Boynton, Peter Starbird
  - Bradley, Walter Parke
  - Braginski, Benjamin Martin
  - Braxton, Anthony
  - Brennan, Michael
  - Breaer, Lee
  - Briggs, Morton Winfield
  - Brightman, Edgar Sheffield
  - Brockunier, Samuel Hugh
  - Brody, Nathan
  - Bromberg, Marcia
  - Brown, James R.
  - Brown, Judith C.
  - Brown, Norman Oliver
  - Brown, Ralph H.
  - Brown, Robert E. Bob
  - Bruce, Neely
  - Bruce, Phyllis
  - Bruno, Joe
  - Brush, Lorelei R.
  - Bruster, Donald C.
  - Budryk, Peter
  - Bueno, Emily de la Torre
  - Buel, Richard Van Wyck Jr.
  - Bueno, Jose Rollin de la Torre
  - Burford, Gilbert
  - Burns, Gerald T.
  - Burry, Allan
  - Busson, Thomas Wainright
  - Butler, Jeffrey Ernest
  - Butterfield, Katerina Geyer
  - Butler, Judy
  - Callisen, Sterling Adolph
  - Cameron, Ron
  - Campbell, Nancy and Campbell Family
  - Campbell, Thomas Moody
  - Carby, Hazel
  - Carey, Drew A.
  - Carlton, Jill Margo
  - Carr, John
  - Casey Michael
  - Caspari, Ernst Wolfgang
  - Cater, Douglass
  - Catton, Bruce
  - Chace, Joan
  - Chambers, Anthony H.
  - Charles, Douglas
  - Chee, Alexander
  - Cherniavsky, Michael
  - Chernoff, Barry
  - Chick, Edson Mariand
  - Churchill, William L.
  - Clark, Katerina
  - Clark, Norris Berkeley
  - Clark, Richard Guthrie
  - Clawson, Mary Ann
  - Cochrane, Vincent Winner
  - Cohan, Frederick
  - Cohen, Rev. Gerald Philip
  - Cohen, Nina T.
  - Cole, George
  - Cole, Joseph W.
  - Coley, William Bradley
  - Collins, Karen
  - Comfort, W. Wistar
  - Commons, John Rogers
  - Comstock, Gary
  - Compton, Kevin J.
  - Conklin, George Newton
  - Conley, Carey Herbert
  - Conley, James
  - Conn, Herbert William
  - Connor, Anthony
  - Cook, Frederick G.
  - Coughlan, Neil Patrick
  - Coughlan Phillippa
  - Coven, Ethan Monroe
  - Cowdery, Lauren
  - Cowie, Alexander
  - Crader, Diana
  - Craig, Barbara H.
  - Creeger, George Raymond
  - Creighton, Joanne
  - Crenshaw, Martha
  - Crimmins, Cathy
  - Crites, Stephen Decator
  - Crosby, Christina
  - Crossley, Moses Leverock
  - Crouse, Anne
  - Cruz-Saco, Maria
  - Culliton, Richard
  - Culotta, Sheryl
  - Cunard, Manny
  - Cunningham, Paul Jerome
  - Curran, Andrew
  - Currott, David Richard
  - Curtis Michael
  - Curts, Paul Holroyd
  - Cutler, Alan R.
  - Cutler, Cheryl
  - Cutler, Jonathan
  - Cutting, James
  - Daley, Anthony
  - Daltry, Joseph Samuel
  - Daltry, Majorie Rice
  - Danahy, Michael
  - Daniels, Norman Joseph
  - Daniels, Winthrop More
  - Danner, Norman
  - Darr, John Whittier
  - Darsono, Soekanto S.
  - Davis, Farina M.
  - Deboer, Fredrik Eugene
  - deBoer, Jelle
  - Debold, Richard C.
  - Degiovanni, Fernando
  - Devoto, Stephen
  - DiGiorgio, Michael
  - Dillard, Annie
  - Dillon, William J.
  - Dixon, C. Estelle
  - Dodge, Raymond
  - DOench, Ellen G.
  - Donady, J. James
  - Drake, Durant
  - Dries, Danny
  - Driscoll, Gina
  - Drury, Thomas
  - Ducille, Ann
  - Dudley, Robert
  - Dulchin, Joan
  - Dunham, Theodore Chadbourne
  - Dunn, Peter N.
  - Dupuy, Alex
  - Durbin, John Price
  - Durkin, Michael J.
  - Dutcher, George Matthew
  - Dyson, Stephen Lee
  - Eastman, Edith L.
  - Eaton, Vernet Eller
  - Ebrecht Ron
  - Eck, Thomas
  - Ederer, Jeff
  - Edgar, John Blanchard
  - Edwards, Jane
  - Ehlers, Reba C.
  - Eichelberger, William Snyder
  - Eisner, Marc
  - Eldridge, Donald A.
  - Ellis, Frederich
  - Elphick, Richard
  - Ennis, Philip Harry
  - Everett, John Rutherford
  - Fabian, Johannes
  - Fahlund G. Gregory
  - Fair, Ronald
  - Faller, James Elliot
  - Faller, Larry Dean
  - Farley, Frank Edgar
  - Farrand, Max
  - Farrington, James (Jim)
  - Faust, Albert Bernhardt
  - Fauver, Edgar Doc
  - Fay, Brian
  - Felshin, Nina
  - Ferrero, Bonnie
  - Fesler, Wesley Eugene
  - Feuer, Willie
  - Field, Richard S.
  - Fife, Robert Herndon
  - Files, Steven
  - Finn, John
  - Firshein, William
  - Fisher, Clyde Olin
  - Fisher, Willard Clark
  - Fisher, Sue
  - Fisk, Ruth Deck
  - Fletcher, Emory
  - Flewelling, Rebecca
  - Foss, Harriet Campbell
  - Foster, Malcolm Cecil
  - Foster, Susan Leigh
  - Foye, Wilbur Garland
  - Foyle, Douglas
  - Francisco, William
  - Franco, Rose
  - Francisco, William H.
  - Franklin, H. Bruce
  - Frazer, John Thatcher
  - Frazer, Susan
  - Frederiksen, Nancy A.
  - Frederiksen, Nils
  - Frenzel, Peter Michael
  - Friedberg, Harris
  - Frohock, Wilbur Merrill
  - Fry, Albert Joseph
  - Fusso, Susanne Grace
  - Gallarotti, Giulio
  - Gargan, Edward T.
  - Garrett, George Palmer
  - Garrett, Ruth H.
  - Gates, Lisa
  - Gaudon, Sheila
  - Gecewicz, Lucille
  - Gelb, Leslie H.
  - Gemeinhardt, Laurence Edwin
  - Giammatteo, John
  - Gilden, Katya Alpert
  - Gillmor, Charles Stewart
  - Gilmore, Martha
  - Gil-Ordonez, Angel
  - Ginsburg, Faye
  - Ginsberg, Marsha
  - Gitay, Xehoshua
  - Glaz, Sarah
  - Glanton, Paul
  - Glidden, Hope
  - Goel, Namni
  - Golob, Eugene Owen
  - Gomez-Ibanez, Jose
  - Gonzalez, Antonio
  - Gooding, William Lambert
  - Goodrich, Diana Sorensen
  - Goodrich, Hubert Baker
  - Gortner, Ross Aiken
  - Gottschalk, Peter
  - Gottschalk, Walter Helbig
  - Gourevitch, Jacqueline
  - Gourevitch, Victor
  - Grabel, Laura
  - Grame, Theodore Charles
  - Green, Samuel Magee
  - Greene, F. B.
  - Greene, Nathaniel
  - Greene, Richard Leighton
  - Greengard, Carola
  - Greenhill, Kelly M.
  - Greenleaf, William Eber
  - Greenstein, Fred I.
  - Griffen, Frank Loxley
  - Grockowski, Walter
  - Gropp, Paul Eugene
  - Grossman, Richard
  - Grover, Elizabeth
  - Gruen, Lori
  - Gruenberg, Barry
  - Grumm, John Grant
  - Grumm, Phyllis Hughes
  - Gustafson, Bessie M.
  - Gutmann, James T.
  - Guy, James M.
  - Guziak, Ronald D.
  - Haagen, ConradHess
  - Haake, Paul C.
  - Hackett, John P.
  - Hager, Anthony Wood
  - Halberg, Jean Goodman
  - Halton, Moshe
  - Hall, Peter
  - Hallie, Philip Paul
  - Hallowell, Burton Crosby
  - Hanson, Earl Dorchester
  - Henson, James Stephen
  - Harmon, Justin
  - Harrington, Karl Pomoroy
  - Harrington, Calvin S.
  - Harris, Michael
  - Harrop, Arthur Henry
  - Harvey, Ian
  - Harvey, Peter
  - Hassan, Ihab Habib
  - Hawkins, Sherman H.
  - Hayes, Aden
  - Hedrick, Joan D.
  - Hebert, Marianne
  - Heidel, William Arthur
  - Heidman, Walter H. Jr.
  - Heisch Allison
  - Helfer, James Stone
  - Henney, Thomas Gonde
  - Henry, Eugenia May
  - Herbst, William
  - Herge, Henry Curtis
  - Hewitt, Joseph William
  - Hibbard, Ralph G.
  - Higgins, Jon B.
  - Higgins, Scott
  - Hiles, Hannah
  - Hill, Freddye
  - Hill, George Albert
  - Hill, Henry Allen
  - Hill, Patricia
  - Hingorani, Manju
  - Hinkson Craig, Barbara
  - Hirsch, Susan
  - Hitchcock, Henry-Russell
  - Drawer 4D
  - Hoberman, Louisa Schell
  - Hoffman, Frank Sargent
  - Hogendorn, Christopher
  - Hoggard, Jay
  - Hoitsma, David
  - Holdich, Joseph
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell
  - Holmes, Scott G.
  - Holzberg, Jules Donald
  - Hoover, Charles Ruggles
  - Horgan, Paul (2)
  - Horne, Gregory S.
  - Horst, Steven
  - Howard, Lise Marie
  - Howell, Susie and Chip
  - Howland, Leroy Albert
  - Hoyt, Margaret
  - Hoyt, Peter
  - Huber, Jacob Frederick
  - Hughes, Gertrude
  - Huhn, Tom
  - Hunter-Union, Lori
  - Humphrey, George
  - Hunderlach, John F. Jack
  - Huntsberry, Randall
  - Hurwitz, Isaac David
  - Huwel, Lutz
  - Hyman, Herbert H.
  - Idzerda, Stanley J.
  - Infante, Anthony A.
  - Isenberg, Charles
  - Isenberg, Noah
  - Istrail, Soren
  - Jacobi, Peter A.
  - Jacobsen, Joyce
  - Jaffe, David
  - James, T. C.
  - James, Thomas
  - Jauregui, Benigno S.
  - Jenkins, Ron
  - Jensen, Rick
  - Jimenez, Juan Carlos Perez
  - Johnson, Allan G.
  - Johnston, John
  - Jones, Barbara
  - Jones, Victor
  - Joyce, Jon Michael
  - Joyell, Christopher
  - Jurale, Joan
  - Kahn, Coppelia
  - Kahn, Judd
  - Kennam, Thomas
  - Karamcheti, Indira
  - Katz, Adam
  - Katz, Dalit
  - Katz, Wallace Barry
  - Kearns, Naomi
  - Keiser, Robert Lincoln
  - Kerr, William
  - Kerr-Ritchie, Jeff
  - Kibel, Alvin
  - Kiefer, Barry
  - Kilby, Peter
  - Killen, Melanie
  - Kinney, Harry
  - Kirn, John
  - Klaaren, Eugene Marion
  - Kleinberg, Ethan
  - Kleczkowski, Claudette
  - Klinger, Uwe R.
  - Knapp, Robert Hampden
  - Knight, William Nicholas
  - Koerting, Fran
  - Kohler, Bryan E.
  - Kohs, Ellis
  - Konerding, Erhard
  - Konstan, J. David
  - Kosinski, Maria
  - Kostacopoulos, Pete
  - Kramer, Ilyse
  - Kratzer, Karen
  - Ku, Tim
  - Kuan, Frank
  - Kuehale, John
  - Kuenzli, Katherine
  - Kuivila, Ron
  - Kupo, Leilani
  - Kupstas, James
  - Lacock, Darrell D.
  - Landan, Susan
  - Landborn, Adair
  - Landsberg, Dave
  - Lane, Robert
  - Langhout, Regina
  - Langlie, Theos Alvin
  - Larsen, Ronald John
  - Lash, Dale William
  - Later, Max
  - Lawson, Paula
  - Lebergott, Stanley
  - Lebergott, Steven D.
  - Lehoucq, Fabrica
  - Leipziger, David
  - Lemert, Charles C.
  - Lensing, Leo
  - Lewis, Gwendolyn
  - Levak, Zarko David
  - Levreault, Russell M.
  - Limbach, Russell Theodore
  - Lindquist, Richard W.
  - Linton, Fred
  - Long, Donald
  - Long, Jerome H.
  - Loper, Samuel Ward
  - Lopez, Robert S.
  - Lovell, Michael Christopher
  - Lowrie, Joyce Oliver
  - Lucid, Robert Francis
  - Lucier, Alvin
  - Lukens, Lewis Nelson
  - Lynch, Carol B.
  - Lynch, G. Robert
  - MacEachern, Barbara
  - Mackil, Emily
  - Magnano, Sebastian
  - Maguire, John David
  - Maines, Clark
  - Manchester, William
  - Mangone, Gerald Joseph
  - Manzo, Louis A.
  - Markgraf, Bruce R.
  - Markovits, Andrei S.
  - Martin, John
  - Martin, John Frederick
  - Masters, Bruce
  - Mather, William Williams
  - McAlear, Michael A.
  - McAlister, Liza
  - McAllester, David Park
  - McCann, Sean
  - McCarthy, Bob
  - McCarthy, Susan Bridge
  - McConaughy, Elizabeth
  - McCurdy, Hugh Graham
  - McDermott, Cari
  - McDermott, William H.
  - McGann, Heather
  - McGeoch, John Alexander
  - McGuire, James
  - McKenna, Gertrude Mary
  - McIntosh, John S.
  - McMahon, Joseph Henry
  - McMann, George Steward
  - Mednick, Jonathan
  - Meerts, John
  - Meislahn, Nancy Hargrave
  - Melley, Pat
  - Mensah, Helen
  - Meyer, Donald B.
  - Meyer, Priscilla A.
  - Mezey, Susan Gluck
  - Michael, Ben
  - Michelot, Philippe F.
  - Miel, Jan
  - Miglus, Wlaayslaw
  - Miles, Walter Richard
  - Millbrooke, Anne Marie
  - Miller, Charles Anthony
  - Miller, Clyde Horace Jr.
  - Miller, Daniel R.
  - Miller, David
  - Miller, Gary M.
  - Miller, Irwin
  - Miller, James Arthur
  - Miller, Joan
  - Miller, Merrill P.
  - Miller, Norman
  - Miller, Richard Alan
  - Miller, William I.
  - Millett, Fred Benjamin
  - Millinger, James Ferguson
  - Milroy, Elizabeth
  - Milutinovic, Zoran
  - Mink, Helen Patterson
  - Mink, Louis O.
  - Mitchell, Arthur
  - Mitchell, Douglas
  - Mirza, Mahan
  - Modigliani, Vito
  - Mohan, Pandiri Sarasvati
  - Montero, Janine
  - Montgomery, Christopher
  - Moon, James D.
  - Moore, Basil John
  - Moran, Edward
  - Morawski, Jill
  - Moreno-Nuno, Carmen
  - Morgan, David Walter
  - Morgan, Janet
  - Morgan, Thomas J.
  - Morrison, Jane W.
  - Mueller, Marnie W.
  - Mukerji, Ishita
  - Mullis, Duncan Philip
  - Mulvey, Irene Teresa
  - Munich, Adrienne Auslander
  - Murphy, Carole Housley
  - Murphy, Geraldine Joanne
  - Murphy, James Thomas
  - Murphy, Russell Davis
  - Murray, Terry L.
  - Musser, Curtis Allen
  - Musser, Frederic O.
  - Myers, Cheryl M.
  - Myers, Jack W.
  - Myerowitz, Rachel
  - Myers, Robert
  - Nadler, Harry
  - Naegele, Janice R.
  - Naftalevich, Aaron
  - Naipaul, V. S.
  - Nakamura, Haruji
  - Nakhimovsky, Lina
  - Napier, A. H.
  - Nasciemento, Claudia Tatinge
  - Nash, Henry T.
  - Nathanson, Alan J.
  - Nations, Harold L.
  - Neal, Ronald L.
  - Needler, Howard
  - Neil, Edward J.
  - Nelligan, Bill
  - Nelson, David
  - Nelson, Fred A.
  - Nerenberg, Ellen
  - Neumann, Sigmund
  - Neville, Charles W.
  - Newbury, Catharine M.
  - Newbury, David S.
  - Newcomer, Sam Harold
  - Newman, Deena T. J.
  - Ngaliman, S.
  - Nicolson, Frank Walter
  - Noll, William
  - Norris, Steve
  - North, Douglas McKay
  - Notopoulos, James Anestasios
  - Novack, Cynthia
  - Novelly, Robert A.
  - Novick, Stewart
  - Nowakowski, Kathie
  - Ntlabata, Gladstone
  - Nussdorfer, Laurie
  - Oberlander, Andrew James
  - OConnell, Suzanne
  - Octjen, Emily M.
  - OGorman, Hubert J.
  - Ohmann, Carol
  - Ohmann, Richard Malin
  - OLeary, James J.
  - Olin, Julia Mathilda (Lynch)
  - Oliver, Don
  - Olson, Lawrence Alexander
  - O Meally, Robert G.
  - Ormsby, Elizabeth
  - Ostor, Akos
  - Overstreet, Alan Burr
  - Page, Thornton Leigh
  - Paglia, Camille A.
  - Palamountain, Joseph C.
  - Palley, Thomas I.
  - Palmer, Vivian
  - Palumbo, John E.
  - Pandisher, Jeremiah M.
  - Panning, William H.
  - Paoletti, John T.
  - Pappu, Suguna
  - Parker, Jane K.
  - Parker, Wyman West
  - Parslow, Christopher Charles
  - Parsons, J. E.
  - Pasco-Pranger, Molly
  - Patalano, Andrea
  - Patnaik, P. Satyanarayana
  - Paton, Diana R.
  - Paton, John W. Jack
  - Patton, Peter
  - Paul, Michael E.
  - Pauli, Adolph Frederick
  - Pawel, Laura
  - Pawlowski, Philip J.
  - Payne, James L.
  - Peck, Walter Edwin
  - Peltz, Ratchmiel
  - Pendleton, Ralph
  - Peoples, Joe Webb
  - Perlis, Vivian
  - Perlman, Marc
  - Perry, Irene
  - Perry, Edward A. Jr.
  - Perron, Diana
  - Pessagno, J. Meric
  - Pessl, Fred Jr.
  - Peszke, Michael A.
  - Peters, Sally
  - Peterson, Gerald A.
  - Petersson, George A.
  - Petrill, Steven
  - Petterson, Edith
  - Petty, Marguerite G.
  - Pfeifer, Richard M.
  - Phelan, Timothy S.
  - Philip, A. G. Davis
  - Philips, J. Christopher
  - Phillips, David
  - Phillips, Robert L.
  - Pigoni, Dolores A.
  - Pillarella, John J.
  - Pillay, Anand
  - Plagenhoef, Garry A.
  - Plagenhoef, Stanley Clifford
  - Platt, Austin, Pickard
  - Plese, Zlatko
  - Plous, Scott
  - Plush, Vincent
  - Poch, Bruce J.
  - Poggi, Barbara
  - Point, Francoise
  - Polate, Levana
  - Pollack, David
  - Polier, Nicole
  - Polsby, Nelson
  - Pomper, Philip
  - Pope, Alan MacKenzie
  - Porter Stephen
  - Pothier, John T.
  - Potter, Claire
  - Potter, S. Steven
  - Potts, David B.
  - Poursine, Kay
  - Pratt, Rex F.
  - Prentice, George
  - Pribram, Helen B.
  - Price, Alan D.
  - Price, Charles T.
  - Price, E. Curmie
  - Price, Melanye
  - Price, Robin
  - Pringle, Wallace Carthcart
  - Proffitt, Dennis R.
  - Proskurina, Dr. Vera J.
  - Proudmer, Valborg
  - Pugh, Mildred
  - Pusey, Nathan M.
  - Pyke, Jenny
  - Radko, Thomas R.
  - Raman, Khrishnan
  - Ramos, Val
  - Ramirez, Miguel D.
  - Randall, David Lindsey
  - Ranganathan, Tanjore
  - Rao, K. Surekha
  - Raphael, Tina
  - Rasmussen, Michelle
  - Rasmussen, Jon A.
  - Ravishanker, Ganesan Ravi
  - Ray, Kasturi
  - Rayburn, Marlon
  - Raymond, Harlow P. Doc
  - Reddy, William Lawrence
  - Redfield, Seth
  - Redpath, Jean
  - Reed, Kit
  - Reed, Joseph Wayne
  - Reeve, Franklin D.
  - Reeves, Robert F.
  - Regalado, Nancy F.
  - Reichenbach, Inge
  - Reid, James D.
  - Rendall, Raymond Eaton
  - Renshaw, Raemer, Rex
  - Retta, Teklehaimanot
  - Reynolds, Paul A.
  - Rhorer, Catherine Campbell
  - Rice Daltry Rosenbaum, Marjorie
  - Rice, William North
  - Rice William North: photos
  - Rich, Sarah Katherine
  - Rich, Wesley Everett
  - Richardson, Robert D. Jr.
  - Richter, Melvin
  - Rider, Fremont
  - Rider, Jeff
  - Riedinger, Anita
  - Risley, John Hollister
  - Risley, Mary Kring
  - Rivera Casellas, Zaira O.
  - Rivers, Sam
  - Roberts, Evelyn B.
  - Roberts, Martin David
  - Roberts, Michael J.
  - Robertson, Lewis C.
  - Robinson, Dan
  - Rogan, Claire
  - Rogers, Brian D.
  - Rogers, R. N.
  - Rohrbach, John
  - Rohrer, Judith C.
  - Roiphe, Anne
  - Rois, Javier
  - Rollefson, Robert J.
  - Romano, Renee
  - Rood, Herbert J.
  - Roos, Suzanne
  - Rosa, Edward Bennett
  - Rose, Ernestine
  - Rose, Paul I.
  - Rose, Phyllis Davidoff
  - Rose, Tricia
  - Roseland, Mark L.
  - Rosenbaum, Marjorie R.
  - Rosenbaum, Robert Abraham
  - Rosenberg, Alan Eliott
  - Rosenblat, Tanya
  - Rosenthal, Rob
  - Rosenburg, Alan E.
  - Rosenburg, Joel W.
  - Rosenberg, Rosalind
  - Rosmarin, Leonard
  - Ross, Steven J.
  - Rosseau, Shirley
  - Round, David K.
  - Roura-Parella, Juan
  - Rouse, Joseph
  - Ront, Earl H.
  - Rowan, Sally Blelock
  - Royer, Dana
  - Rozeboom, William
  - Rozwadowski, Franek
  - Rubenstein, Mary-Jane
  - Rudich, Norman
  - Rudolph, Ira
  - Rumberger, Joseph P.
  - Rushdy, Ashraf
  - Rushin, Kate
  - Russell, Allan
  - Russell, Donald MacIntosh
  - Russman, Penny
  - Russu, Irina M.
  - Rutland, Peter
  - Ryan, J. Randolph
  - Sahai, Sharda
  - Saim, Peter
  - Saetonstall, Robert
  - Sainer, Arthur
  - Saks, Rabbi Moshe
  - Salamon, Frank R.
  - Salm, Peter
  - Salzer, John
  - Samuel, Yoshiko Yokochi
  - Sanders, David K.
  - Sanford, Thomas M.
  - Sand, Reihi
  - Satran, David
  - Scalora, Salvatore
  - Scham, Michael
  - Schacter, Bernice Zeldin
  - Schattsneider, Elmer Eric
  - Schatz, Ronald
  - Schell, Jonathan
  - Scheibe, Karl Edward
  - Schiebold, John
  - Schiff, Jeffrey
  - Schmidt, Cynthia Elizabeth
  - Schmitz, William E.
  - Schneider, Edward Christian
  - Schnyder, Walter
  - Schorr, David M.
  - Schorske, Carl Emil
  - Schrempp, Gregory A.
  - Schultz, Arthur Rudolph
  - Schultz, Marjorie Croswell Hill
  - Schulzinger, Robert David
  - Schumacher, Edward J.
  - Schuster, Nancy
  - Schwaber, Paul
  - Schwarcz, Vera
  - Schwartz, Larissa N.
  - Schwartz, Nancy L.
  - Schwarz, Heinrich
  - Schwarzkopf, Dorothea
  - Sciola, Michael
  - Seamon, John G.
  - Sease, John W.
  - Sebera, David Keith
  - Sebrechts, Marc
  - Secord, Linda
  - Seeley, David
  - Seeley, J.
  - Seeley, Tracy
  - Segal, Harry G.
  - Sellers, Charles Coleman
  - Seigh, William R.
  - Sellin, David
  - Selover, David Dudin
  - Sesar, Carl
  - Sforza, Count Carlo
  - Shapira, Nathan Henry
  - Shapiro, Ann-Louise
  - Shapiro, Norman Richard
  - Sharpe, Matthew
  - Sheibe, Karl
  - Shenin, David M. K.
  - Shelemay, Kay K.
  - Shen, Louis Ning-Yao
  - Sheng, Francis M.
  - Shieh, Julia J.
  - Shinohara, Keiji
  - Shloss, Carol
  - Shoemaker, Innis H.
  - Shortt, Rae M.
  - Shotter, John
  - Shubow, Jessica
  - Shulka, Sandhya Rajendra
  - Shutt, Stephen R.
  - Siegenfeld, Stephen R.
  - Siegenfeld, Billy
  - Siff, Michael
  - Sigal, Leon
  - Silverman, Mark P.
  - Silverstein, Joseph
  - Silverbug, Miriam Ron
  - Simmel, Arnold
  - Simmons, Fred
  - Simonetta, Marcello
  - Simonovits, Andras
  - Singer, Michael
  - Singleton, Robert Richmond
  - Sinnamon, Harry M.
  - Siry, Joseph
  - Slobin, Mark
  - Slocum, Frederick
  - Slotkin, Richard Sidney
  - Smith, Alan Brian
  - Smith, Davis
  - Smith, Gary
  - Smith, Gay
  - Smith, Jean Barr
  - Smith, John Mott
  - Smith, Louis E.
  - Smith, Morton V.
  - Smith, Nancy
  - Smith, Richard Frederick
  - Smith, Suzanne E.
  - Smyers, Karen
  - Sneath, Elias Hershey
  - Snow, Charles Wilbert
  - Snyder, David
  - Snyder, Katherine V.
  - Sobel, Jerry E.
  - Sobelman, Rabbi George
  - Sobel, Joshua
  - Sobolov, Susan B.
  - Sodi, Risa
  - Soedarsono
  - Solazzi, Robert E.
  - Solie, Roger
  - Solomons, Gary Jr.
  - Sottys, Jacqueline R.
  - Sorensen, Diana
  - Sorkin, Carolyn
  - Spaeth, John William, Jr.
  - Spangler, Eve
  - Spear, Gary Neal
  - Spencer, Kevin M.
  - Springer, Carolyn
  - Spurrier, William Atwell
  - Stabler, Ernest
  - Stambler, Moses
  - Stamelman, Richard Howard